export const GeographyQuizOne = [
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Russia:',
        answers: [
            'Minsk',
            'Belegrad',
            'Moscow',
            'St. Petersburg'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Moscow'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Norway:',
        answers: [
            'Oslo',
            'Helsinki',
            'Stockholm',
            'Prague'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Oslo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Estonia:',
        answers: [
            'Liten',
            'Tallin',
            'Rakvere',
            'Vilnius'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tallin'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of India:',
        answers: [
            'New Delhi',
            'Bangladesh',
            'Bombai',
            'Islamabad'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'New Delhi'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Japan:',
        answers: [
            'Osaka',
            'Nairobi',
            'Tokio',
            'Osawa'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Tokio'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Australia:',
        answers: [
            'Melbourne',
            'Sydney',
            'Canberra',
            'Ottawa'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Canberra'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Canada:',
        answers: [
            'Québec',
            'Calgary',
            'New Portland',
            'Ottawa'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Ottawa'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Brazil:',
        answers: [
            'Brazilia',
            'Rio de Janeiro',
            'Bogotá',
            'Santa Marta'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Brazilia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Egypt:',
        answers: [
            'Nairobi',
            'Giza',
            'Luxor',
            'Cairo'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Cairo'
    },
    {
        question: 'Capital city of Italy:',
        answers: [
            'Rome',
            'Venice',
            'Milano',
            'Madrid'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Rome'
    }
]